boxofficemojo.com 2008-05-17

# Box Office Mojo Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Statement for _Box Office Mojo_  
_** _Box Office Mojo_ has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our members and web site visitors. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: _Box Office Mojo_. 

The information that we collect depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. You can visit many pages on our site without providing any information. Other pages may prompt you to provide information, such as when you register for access to portions of our site, sign up for an account, participate in polls, provide feedback, or request interactive features that are present on our site. (e.g., games, chat rooms, forums, message boards, new groups). **Do not provide false information to access any portion of our site**. 

With regards to information that you choose to provide on our site, we encourage you to be careful and responsible. Should you choose to voluntarily disclose any personal information on our site be aware that such information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and this policy.

We also collect information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to you. We may log the name of your Internet Service Provider, IP address, or use "cookie" technology to assist us with enhancing your experience on our site, including but not limited to troubleshooting our web site or server (which may require third party technical support), site administration, using cookies to store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or to control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but be aware that doing so may limit your ability to access certain portions of the site or may require you to re-enter your user name and password. Additionally, refusing cookies may prevent us from being able to customize the site's features according to your preferences. 

**_Third Party Sites_**  
We expect our partners, advertisers and third party affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. However, third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on our page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through our site you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, web sites, advertisements, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. We are not responsible for the actions, privacy, security or content of such third parties. If you are asked to provide information on one of these Web sites, we encourage you carefully to review their privacy policy before sharing your information. 

**_Advertisers  
_** As you access our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before to develop target advertising data. Through features available on our site, third parties may use cookies or other technology to gather information. Although these activities will appear to be coming from our site, they are actually coming directly from the third parties. We do not control the use of this technology or the resulting information and are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. 

**_Your Contact Information_**  
You may, in the course of using our site, choose to provide us with personal information about yourself including name and e-mail address. We will not sell or give away your name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number to any third parties. We do reserve the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Box Office Mojo, LLC or substantially all of its assets. 

We may disclose your information in response to a court order, to enforce our [terms of use](http://www.boxofficemojo.com/about/termsofuse.htm), at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law and/or whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary to give such information to law enforcement authorities. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases. 

**_Choice to Opt-Out_**  
We sometimes permit our advertising and promotional partners to e-mail you about services, features, products, special offers and unique content we believe might interest you. If you prefer not to receive e-mail communications sent directly from our advertisers or promotional partners, you will be given an opportunity to decline before you provide us information we might use for this purpose. If you decline at the time you provide us such information, we will not share the personal information you provide. If you continue to receive such information, contact us at [info@boxofficemojo.com](mailto:info@boxofficemojo.com) and we will remove your information from our database. 

**_Children  
_** We comply with all applicable laws and regulations, including the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), which requires the consent of a parent or guardian for the collection of personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of the law, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe that we have any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below. 

**_Changes to This Policy  
_** We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected. 

**_Governing Law  
_** This policy and the use of this Site are governed by California law. Any claim related to the Site or this policy shall be brought in a federal or state court in Los Angeles, California within one year after the claim arises. You agree no such claim may be brought as a class action. Users of our site consent to the jurisdiction and venue of such court as the most convenient and appropriate for the resolution of disputes concerning this policy. We are controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United States. If you are located outside the United States, please note the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. You hereby consent to this transfer. 

In the event case of any conflict between the terms of this policy and the terms of any electronic or machine readable privacy policy (for example, a P3P electronic privacy policy), the terms of this written policy shall control. 

**_Contacting the Web Site_**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

Sean Saulsbury  
Box Office Mojo, LLC  

**_RELATED LINK_**  
 **•[ _Box Office Mojo_ Terms of Use](http://www.boxofficemojo.com/about/termsofuse.htm)**

® 2007 and Copyright © 1998-2008 [**Box Office Mojo, LLC**](mailto:info@boxofficemojo.com). All rights reserved.  
Charts and data cannot be published or posted elsewhere without the expressed permission of Box Office Mojo. To publish or use the stats for professional purposes, please inquire at [info@boxofficemojo.com](mailto:info@boxofficemojo.com).
